$opubes_option_obody_manual_behaviour	OBody preset change
$opubes_option_shaved_chance	Shaved Chance
$opubes_option_normal_chance	Normal Chance
$opubes_option_stylish_chance	Stylish Chance
$opubes_option_hairy_chance	Hairy Chance
$opubes_option_pube_cycle_key	Cycle pubes key
$opubes_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$opubes_message_box_option_no	No
$opubes_highlight_obody_manual_behaviour	Set what happens to the pubes when you manually change a character's preset with OBody:\nDon't change pubes: Current pubes (or lackthereof) will not be changed\nRandomize pubes: Pubes will be randomized everytime you change a character's preset manually\nAsk before changing pubes: A prompt will appear asking if you want new pubes to be chosen randomly for the character
$opubes_highlight_shaved_chance	Set the chance for characters to have shaved pubes. The sum of Shaved+Normal+Stylish+Hairy chances must be 100.
$opubes_highlight_normal_chance	Set the chance for characters to have normal pubes. The sum of Shaved+Normal+Stylish+Hairy chances must be 100.
$opubes_highlight_stylish_chance	Set the chance for characters to have styled pubes. The sum of Shaved+Normal+Stylish+Hairy chances must be 100.
$opubes_highlight_hairy_chance	Set the chance for characters to have hairy pubes. The sum of Shaved+Normal+Stylish+Hairy chances must be 100.
$opubes_highlight_cycle_key	Set the key to cycle randomly between pubes for the character in the crosshair. If no character is in your crosshair, it will cycle randomly between pubes for your Player Character. Set to ESC to disable this key entirely.
$opubes_highlight_pube_actor	Select a random pube of the chosen style to the character that is selected in the crosshair. If no pube texture of the chosen type is found, the character's pubes will not be changed.
